{
  "name" : "SAMPLE IMPORT DECK",
  "cards" : [ {
    "question" : "Solve 1 + 1.",
    "answer" : "2",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ "Math" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "What is 10 - 10?",
    "answer" : "0",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ "Math" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "What is 8 * 8?",
    "answer" : "64",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ "Math" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "Evaluate 1024 / 2.",
    "answer" : "512",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ "Math" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "Hello?",
    "answer" : "World",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ "CS", "Simple" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "Are there any tag?",
    "answer" : "No",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ ]
  }, {
    "question" : "Is this card unique?",
    "answer" : "Yes it is.",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ ]
  }, {
    "question" : "Which later is HTTP at?",
    "answer" : "Application",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ "CS2105" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "What transport does HTTP use?",
    "answer" : "TCP",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ "CS2105" ]
  }, {
    "question" : "What is the status code for OK in HTTP?",
    "answer" : "200",
    "totalRating" : 0,
    "numberOfAttempts" : 0,
    "tags" : [ "CS2105" ]
  } ]
}